William Leo

Blockchain developer

Canada

SUMMARY

Resourceful Blockchain Developer with 5 years of experience in software engineering. Co-founded ConanSwap, a DEX with 20,000 active supporters. Mastered Solidity, JavaScript, Golang, and Python. Extensive knowledge in smart contracts, consensus algorithms, and data structures. Looking for a job as a Blockchain Developer that will allow me to build the financial system of tomorrow.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Blockchain developer (Remote Job), Paul Bauder GmbH

06/2022 - 09/2023

• Closely collaborated with the product and dev teams to improve the efficiency of the platform by 25%

Stuttgart, Germany

- Built 5 reusable cross-chain libraries
- Participated in the development of 3 new tools and integrated them into the platform
- Assisted in developing the backend that became the foundation for the intersection between Web3 and FinTech
- Participated in 5+ open source community projects, met with stakeholders, and mentored and tutored 3 junior developers

Blockchain developer, Qupital

03/2020 - 05/2022

Ottawa, Canada

- Developed 16 decentralized social media web applications using React, CSS, Bootstrap, and web3.js/Ethers for integrating Ethereum.
- Reduced costs by 40% using an Ethereum smart contract to automate supply chain management processes.
- Built a private blockchain using Hyperledger Fabric 1.0 that enhanced data security and reduced risk exposure by 93%.
- Created and launched 12 decentralized applications based on RW's \$150M daily transaction using Ethereum's smart contracts.

Blockchain Developer, UL Solutions

02/2018 - 02/2020

Ottawa, Canada

- \bullet Developing DApps using HTML, CSS, ReactJS, NodeJS, JavaScript
- Coding smart contracts with solidity programing
- Running personal Blockchain for ethereum development using Ganache and Truffle Develop
- Providing secured data provenance in Healthcare
- Developing functional solutions in exchanging sensitive health records implementing Blockchain.
- Developing condition-based contracts using solidity and deploying smart contracts in Testrpc

EDUCATION

SKILLS

Blockchain

DApp, Web3, Solidity, Bitcoin, Ethereum

Full-Stack

MERN, LAMP, Django

Database

Oracle, TeraData, MongoDB, MySQL

Services

Marketplace Site Blockchain Learning Ecommerce Development